ironspeed.com 2017-12-04

# Iron Speed

_Last updated on January 17, 2008_

Iron Speed is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement applies to the Iron Speed Web site and our Iron Speed Designer software. Please read the complete Iron Speed privacy statement. 

## Collection of your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing and/or registering Iron Speed products. Personal information collected by Iron Speed often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. 

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase from the Iron Speed Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number. 

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site. 

Iron Speed also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, MAC address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Iron Speed Web pages and software. 

Iron Speed Designer periodically validates your product key when you start the application. This validation is to ensure that key being used is a valid key. During validation, the information that is sent to the computer includes the IP Address, MAC Address, and other information. Iron Speed Designer may also connect to our servers when you use the product activation dialog, online help (documentation), or submit a technical support case. 

Iron Speed also collects information about which pages our customers visit in the course of using Iron Speed Web sites and software. 

When you use certain Iron Speed Web sites or software, you will be asked to provide your e-mail address and a password to sign you in. 

## Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:  |  | To ensure appropriate product use  
---|---  
| To ensure our site is relevant to your needs  
| To deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase  
| To help us create and publish content most relevant to you  
| To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Iron Speed  
| To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate  
  
We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. We may combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content or support. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Iron Speed may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Iron Speed or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Iron Speed, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Iron Speed employees, users of Iron Speed products or services, or members of the public. 

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Iron Speed or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using our site or software, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

## Control of your Personal Information

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Iron Speed will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

Iron Speed occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services. 

Iron Speed may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen. 

## Security of your Personal Information

Iron Speed is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

## Protection of Children's Personal Information

Iron Speed is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 

## Use of Cookies

When someone uses Iron Speed’s site or software, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above. 

We also use cookies to collect information on which links are clicked by customers. This information is used to better understand how our users interact with our Web site and software. 

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics). We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information; it is a tool we use to compile statistics about usage of Iron Speed Web sites and software. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies. 

## Changes to this Statement

Iron Speed will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, Iron Speed will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.
